{
    "subject": "resource/Poseidon_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/screenplay",
    "object": "resource/Mark_Protosevich",
    "human_readable": "The screenplay of the film Poseidon is written by Mark Protosevich.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9598710536956787,
            "question": "Besides Poseidon, what other films has Mark Protosevich written screenplays for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9596378207206726,
            "question": "Who wrote the screenplay for the film Poseidon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9347977638244629,
            "question": "Which film features a screenplay by Mark Protosevich?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9338322877883911,
            "question": "Mark Protosevich is known for writing which film's screenplay?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.920708954334259,
            "question": "Name the screenwriter behind the Poseidon movie."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9034968614578247,
            "question": "What kind of work did Mark Protosevich do on the film Poseidon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8865851759910583,
            "question": "What is the name of the screenwriter for the movie Poseidon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7304492592811584,
            "question": "Is Mark Protosevich a screenwriter? What evidence supports this?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5794375538825989,
            "question": "What are some common themes or elements found in Mark Protosevich's screenplays?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43893903493881226,
            "question": "How might the screenplay of Poseidon influence the audience's perception of the story?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The screenplay of the film Poseidon is written by Mark Protosevich.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5366_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes or elements found in Mark Protosevich's screenplays?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5366_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Mark Protosevich a screenwriter? What evidence supports this?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5366_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the screenwriter for the movie Poseidon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5366_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5366_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5366_141.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5366_143.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5366_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5366_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5366_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5366_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5366_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5366_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5366_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents explicitly state that \"Poseidon\" was written by Mark Protosevich. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain multiple references to the screenplay of the film Poseidon, including:\n\n* In the file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5366/re-ranker-msmarco/23.txt`, it is mentioned that the screenplay was written by Mark Protosevich.\n* In the same file path, it is also mentioned that the screenplay was \"Screenplay By Mark Protosevich\".\n* In the file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5366/re-ranker-msmarco/138.txt`, it is explicitly stated that the screenplay was written by Mark Protosevich.\n* Additionally, in the file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5366/re-ranker-msmarco/93.txt` and `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5366/re-ranker-msmarco/140.txt`, Mark Protosevich is mentioned as the screenwriter of Poseidon.\n\nAll these references support the statement that the screenplay of the film Poseidon was written by Mark Protosevich."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the screenplay writer for the film Poseidon, stating that it was written by Mark Protosevich. Therefore, the query \"The screenplay of the film Poseidon is written by Mark Protosevich\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}